presenting icici lombard vector-borne
disease cover this policy protects you
with a cover of up to 75 000 rupees for
malaria as well as other specific
vector-borne diseases this means that
you can focus on your recovery instead
of hospitalization costs
the policy is exclusively available to
free pay card members for a premium of
just
379 rupees inclusive of all taxes you
can also avail a tax benefit under
section 80d
and all it takes is three easy steps
simply visit freepayonline.com
enter your details and the activation
code
complete the verification process and
get your policy it's just that simple
the policy gives you coverage for one
year and is available to everyone
between the age of 18 and 65 years
an initial waiting period of 30 days
would be applicable for this cover
and that's not all
the claims process is simple and
seamless and can be initiated by a call
email or on our website
you can also track the status of your
claim online
so what are you waiting for
promise yourself protection and peace of
mind today
icici lombard
nepali
[Music]